www-answers.com 2011-06-03

# Privacy Policy - Www Answers Games

This privacy policy describes how we treat personal information when you visit and/or use www-answers.com (also referred to as the site, the website). If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us.

**Automatically logged information**

Like most servers, our server automatically record the page requests made when users visit our website. These "server logs" typically include your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language and the date and time of your request. We use this information to help diagnose problems, view statistics for our website and allows us to improve the overall user-experience.

**Contact**

When you contact us through e-mail, by using a contact form or any of the e-mail addresses listed on our website, you're providing us with personal information such as your name and e-mail address. Such information is used only for the purpose of assisting you with, and validating, your inquiry or submission.

**Forms**

By using our search form, you enter a "search term" which will be used to search through the content of our website. This search term will be stored internally, in combination with your IP address. We may use this information to find out what our visitors are searching for so we can determine if our content matches the visitor's interest. We delete this information typically every few weeks and it will only be used to help us improve our website.

**Advertisers**

To serve advertisements on this website, we have teamed up with several advertisers. These ads may contain cookies which are collected by the ad server companies, and we do not have access to this information. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, please consult the following privacy policies:

  * <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>
  * <http://www.valueclickmedia.com/privacy.shtml>
  * <http://www.casalemedia.com/privacy.html>
  * <http://solutions.focalex.com/webgamesprivacy.aspx>

**Games**

The majority of games listed on this website are licensed or used with permission from other, third party websites. We have no control over what data those games may collect. Some games may provide a privacy statement inside the game itself, please read it, if available, before you play a game. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of games we license, or use with permission from third party websites.

**Links**

We may present internal links (i.e. links to our own pages) or external links (i.e. links to other websites) in a format that allows us to track statistics like the number of clicks a link gets. These statistics will only be used to help us improve the website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of websites that are being linked to from our website or newsletter.

**Security**

We protect personal information against such risks as loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, modification or destruction, through appropriate security measures.

 Back to Www Answers Games
